I'm an undesirable, I'm wanted
Why did you choose dark?
Dark will lose
My way is lighting when your way is darkening
I'm not afraid of that dark way going to the light
No one can stop me at this way
I've lost my everything but I never stopped
I'm ready for everything after that
I can be anyone in anywhere but I'm undesirable here
Let's turn on the lights
(God knows I'm one)
I'm not afraid of that dark way going to the light
No one can stop me at this way(even you)
Light see now
Dark is  our mistake
We assembled
We will fight aganist dark
we are not afraid of that dark way going to the light
No one can stop us at this way
Light won, dark lost
Light came first
Cities rising with sun
We won
(God knows we are together)
Don't miss the light
Get it